Every time I wanna die!
So wake up genetic koeyou genkai
So wake up genetic 越えよう限界
erabu michi wa kimattenda shoudou
選ぶ道は決まってんだ　衝動
ima ippen kanashimi kousa shita
今一辺悲しみ交差した
riaru no kitai ga tsumi wo tsudzuku shinri
リアルの期待が罪を続く心理
Which is better? Now it's cold session
Battles are righteous, they're right now
I've got layered consensus
sakaurami de shindokusaisha
逆恨みで新独裁者
Shadow of the messenger I should be
If they've got their saint!
Broken, they'll be here to set you free
yami no shihaisha tte tanoshisou
闇の支配者って楽しそう
Proves you'll never let them set you free
Welcome, sit down now!
Every time I get a chance
I sit between the mirror
And watch them over again
tadashii kikai no kage michibikareteita
正しい機会の影　導かれていた
Every time I lose my flame
Totally in the taillight
What are you waiting for?
This road hikae no tsumi ga kishuu sorou
This road 控えの罪が奇襲揃う
You'll end up where you always start